sellathon.com 2013-03-15

# Sellathon

|    
**This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it and how to correct or change it.**

**What personal information we collect**

Sellathon collects personally identifiable information when you register on our site. The information collected may include any of the following: email, name, IP address, browser information, address, billing address. Any comments or questions you submit are recorded as well. Also, comments about you as a seller or buyer will be collected and may be viewable by other clients. Collection of information takes place at various times while navigating Sellathon’s site and using its software. When entering Sellathon’s site, information may be collected about previous sites the person has viewed. If questions or comments have been submitted via email or a forum on our website, personal information is collected as well.

**Storage of information collected**

All personal information collected is stored via a secure server.

**How we use the information collected**

The goal of collecting customer and viewer information is to create a friendlier, smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while working with Sellathon. Personal information submitted at the time of registration may be used by Sellathon for the marketing and promotion of Sellathon products that we feel may be of interest to you. 

**To whom we disclose personal information**

We take your privacy seriously. You have the right to limit the use of your email address by third parties through the opt-out process available to all Sellathon members. In addition, all email correspondence sent to you by Sellathon will offer an unsubscribe option. If you do not choose to limit the use of your email address, Sellathon may occasionally share this information with carefully selected partner companies whose products and services we feel may be of interest to you. 

**California Law**

Under California law, state residents have the right to request in writing from any business with whom they have a business relationship, (1) a list of categories of personal information, such as name, address email address and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to a third party, if any (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, and (2) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information please email us at info@sellathon.com or send a written request to Sellathon, 527 Flume St, Chico, CA 95928. 

We will respond with thirty (30) days after the receipt of your request. We are only required to provide this information once per calendar year per customer.

**Other information**

By submitting personal information to us or using our site, you agree that we may collect and use such personal information in accordance with our privacy policy or as permitted by law. If you do not agree with these terms, do not provide any personal information to us. If you refuse or withdraw consent, or do not provide us with any necessary personal information, we may not be able to provide you with service. 

**Removal from our Database**

To request removal from the database, file a support request at http://support.sellathon.com/requesthelp.aspx and we will be happy to remove your information immediately. Every email sent to you from Sellathon will also include a link to remove your email address from the mail server. If you request that we modify or remove all of your personal information, we will promptly do so, to the extent possible. Once your personal information has been removed you will not be able to use our services unless you re-register. 

**Children**

Sellathon uses reasonable efforts not to collect, use, or disclose individually identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Our services are not targeted at children, and children may not register for any of our services.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small files on the site that help Sellathon customize the site to assist in creating a better experience for you. Most of the cookies are only "session-cookies" and are deleted from your computer when you log off the site. The use of cookies on our site helps make your visit to the site more efficient. Your browser may allow you to turn off cookies on sites, but could slow down your visit to our site. If you turn off the cookies, you may be asked to re-enter your username and password more often. Cookies are not harmful to your computer.

**Third parties**

Sellathon does have partnerships with companies such as Auctiva. If you do not sign up for a company's products directly on their site, and receive an email from them, do not reply to it. However, if you did sign up for their products directly on their site, you may receive emails from them. If you use their products, but signed up through Sellathon's website, any emails sent about product information or promotions will be filtered through Sellathon's systems and sent out as a Sellathon email. Links to these sites are provided on Sellathon's site and at certain points in the sign up and listing phase of an auction.

**Changing of personal information**

You may edit your personal information at any time by editing Customer Preferences when you are signed in to Sellathon. The new information will be updated in our system and used in the collection of information when visiting Sellathon.

**Merger or Acquisition**

In the event that Sellathon merges or is acquired by another company, all current information Sellathon has will be shared with the other company. Sellathon will do its best to inform you of the transaction.

**Questions, comments, concerns**

All questions, comments and concerns can be submitted via email at info@Sellathon.com. You will receive an answer as soon as possible.

|
